<idea-plugin>
    <id>me.hang.elegant-coding-guide</id>
    <name>Elegant Coding Guide</name>
    <vendor email="hang.wang003354@tongdun.net" url="https://hang.domcer.com/">Hang</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[
    <em>Elegant-Coding-Guide</em><br><br>

    <strong>For English:</strong><br>
    Standardize your code to enhance elegance and readability! This plugin helps you achieve that by providing the following benefits:<br>
    <ol>
        <li><strong>Improved Readability:</strong> A well-defined code style makes your code easier to read and understand.</li>
        <li><strong>Consistency:</strong> Maintaining a consistent coding style helps you and your team to work together more effectively.</li>
        <li><strong>Future-Proofing:</strong> Establishing coding standards now will save you time and effort during future updates and maintenance.</li>
        <li><strong>Detail-Oriented:</strong> A polished code style reflects attention to detail, which is essential for long-term success.</li>
        <li><strong>Reduced Complexity:</strong> Inconsistent code can lead to increased complexity, making maintenance more challenging.</li>
    </ol>
    Remember, while initial code development may be low-cost, significant investment is required for updates and maintenance in the future.<br><br>

    <strong>For Chinese:</strong><br>
    规范代码，让你的代码更加优雅！本插件帮助您实现以下目标：<br>
    <ol>
        <li><strong>提高可读性：</strong>明确的代码风格使代码更易于阅读和理解。</li>
        <li><strong>保持一致性：</strong>维护一致的编码风格有助于您和团队更有效地协作。</li>
        <li><strong>未来适应性：</strong>现在建立编码标准可以在未来的更新和维护中节省时间和精力。</li>
        <li><strong>关注细节：</strong>精致的代码风格体现了对细节的关注，这是长期成功的关键。</li>
        <li><strong>减少复杂性：</strong>不一致的代码会导致复杂性增加，从而使维护变得更加困难。</li>
    </ol>
    请记住，尽管初期开发成本较低，但后期的更新和维护往往需要投入大量的成本。<br>
]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <localInspection
                language="JAVA"
                implementationClass="me.hang.elegant.coding.inspection.ConstantNamingInspection"
                defaultEnabled="true" />

        <applicationConfigurable instance="me.hang.elegant.coding.config.MainConfigurable"
                                 displayName="Elegant Coding Guide"
                                 groupId="appearance"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <action id="me.hang.elegant.coding.HelloWorldAction"
                class="me.hang.elegant.coding.HelloWorldAction"
                text="Say Hello"
                description="Displays a Hello, World message">
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
    </actions>

    <resource-bundle>messages</resource-bundle>
</idea-plugin>